<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Turner</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chris Turner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Two Programming Languages Walk Into A Bar ...</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/10/two-programming-languages-walk-into-a-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/10/two-programming-languages-walk-into-a-bar/</guid>
      <description>Two Programming Lanugages Walk Into A Bar0. IntroductionTwo programming languages walk into The Computation, a new bar in town. Python, a smooth, popular language struts in and nods to the scholars and professionals. They swoon over discussions about everything from machine learning to web development. With a slight delay, R nonchalantly walks in over to its usual spot- next to the Academics and statisticians- surrounded by premade pacakges and libraries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015/07/23/hello-r-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015/07/23/hello-r-markdown/</guid>
      <description>R MarkdownThis is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars)## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID Spike Protein Mutation Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>0. IntroductionCOVID-19 is an infectionus disease caused by Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome Coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2). First identified in December of 2019, SARS-CoV-2 resulted in an ongoing pandemic effecting over 39 million people in 189 countries, but the WHO predicts that with asymptomatic cases, the number of infections may be closer to 800 million.
Therapeutics for those suffering from COVID-19 include collecting and transplanting neautralizing antibodies from patients who have recoved from COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>0. BackgroundFrom the original authors of the dataset: “These are data from one of the first successful trials of adjuvant chemotherapy for colon cancer. Levamisole is a low-toxicity compound previously used to treat worm infestations in animals; 5-FU is a moderately toxic (as these things go) chemotherapy agent. There are two records per person, one for recurrence and one for death.” This porject will explore the follwoing variables AT THE TIME OF DEATH from the colon dataset:Categorical (2-5 groups)- rx Treatment : Obs(ervation), Lev(amisole), Lev(amisole)+5-FU- differ Differentiation of tumour : 1=well, 2=moderate, 3=poor- extent Extent of local spread : 1=submucosa, 2=muscle, 3=serosa, 4=contiguous structures- sex (binary) : 1=male- obstruct (binary) obstruction of colon by tumour : 1=yesNumeric (more than 10 values)- age (numeric) : in years- time (numeric) days until death- nodes (numeric) number of lymph nodes with detectable cancerAfter omitting NA;s, 888 unique partient observations were left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  --</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
